question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
